[
    {
        "question": "What is the nickname of this Air Yeezy 2?",
        "choice": {
            "a": "Red October",
            "b": "Red November",
            "c": "Red December",
            "d": "Red September"
        },
        "answer":"a"
    },

    {
        "question": "What is the number of this shoe, Yeezy Boost … “Turtle Dove”?",
        "answers": [{"answer": "750","juist":true},
            {"answer": "350","juist":false},
            {"answer": "700","juist":false},
            {"answer": "500","juist":false}
        ],
        "type":"MCSA"
    },
    {
        "question": "Wat is mijn naam?",
        "answers": [{"answer": "Ralph","juist":true}],
        "type":"open"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the number of this shoe, Yeezy Boost … “Turtle Dove”?",
        "choice": {
            "1": "750",
            "2": "350",
            "3": "700",
            "4": "500"
        },
        "answer":"2"
    },

    {
        "question": "How many Air Jordan 11 Retro “Concord” did Jordan Brand sold in the late 2018?",
        "choice": {
            "1": "5 million",
            "2": "6 million",
            "3": "500 hundred",
            "4": "1 million"
        },
        "answer":"4"
    },

    {
        "question": "When was the very first Jordan released?",
        
        "answer":"1985"
    },

    {
        "question": "For what sport was the Nike Air Force 1 made?",
        "choice": {
            "1": "Tennis",
            "2": "Basketball",
            "3": "Volleyball",
            "4": "Football"
        },
        "answer":"2"
    },

    {
        "question": "For what ‘Day’ was this released?",
        "choice": {
            "1": "Nike Day",
            "2": "Adidas Day",
            "3": "Air Max Day",
            "4": "Air Force Day"
        },
        "answer":"3"
    },

    {
        "question": "Which company did Jordan collaborate to make this Jordan 5?",
        "choice": {
            "1": "Palace",
            "2": "COMME Des Garçons",
            "3": "Supreme",
            "4": "North Face"
        },
        "answer":"3"
    },

    {
        "question": "Who designed the Off-White X Nike?",
        "choice": {
            "1": "Don-C",
            "2": "Kanye West",
            "3": "Travis Scott",
            "4": "Virgil Abloh"
        },
        "answer":"4"
    },

    {
        "question": "What technology did Kanye West use for the Adidas sole?",
        "choice": {
            "1": "Air",
            "2": "Boost",
            "3": "Gel",
            "4": "React"
        },
        "answer":"2"
    },

    {
        "question": "For which artist was this shoes made?",
        "choice": {
            "1": "Travis Scott",
            "2": "DJ Khaled",
            "3": "JT",
            "4": "Mark Wahlberg"
        },
        "answer":"1"
    }
]